

01138435866



burgsebastian94@gmail.com



in/burgossebastian



burgossebastian.com

Computer Skills
Programming

- HTML
- JavaScript
- CSS
- React

3D Design

- 3D Max
- Rhinoceros
- Maya
- Zbrush

2D Design

- Photoshop
- Autocad
- Ilustrator
- CorelDraw

Video Editing

- Camtasia StudioAfter Effects
- Adobe Premiere Pro

Languages

Spanish: Native

English: Advance/Profesional

Sebastian Exequiel Burgos

Front-End Developer & Designer

About me

Front End Developer and 3D/2D Designer, passionate about computing and technology in constant search to increase my knowledge in the computer field with great facility to learn new tools.

Professionally I have 2 years of experience as a Developer and more than 5 years of experience as an Industrial designer. Besides i have complete studies in 3D Design and animation for cinema, including advanced knowledge in various graphic design and multimedia editing programs.

Experience

Computer technician 2012-2015 Cpufix s.a.

Installation of operating systems and software packages

Software and driver conflict resolution

Industrial Designer 2016-2022 Delcapack s.a.

Design and development of machinery and dies

Cnc Design programming and operation

Maintenance of company computer equipment

Developer Delcapack 2021-2022

Programming plc delta y ISPSoft 3.07

Front End Developer

Freelance Front-End Developer 2022-2023

Web Developer (html, css, javascript, React)

Education

Bachiller Completed

Economics and Accounting

3D Modeling & Animation

3D/2D Design

Multimedia Editing, render y vfx

Front End Developer

Html, css , JavaScript y React

Institute Don Bosco 2011

Delcapack s.a.

Image Campus 2012-2016

CodeCamp 2021